Finding Aid for the Allegra Fuller Snyder papers, 1960-2010 LSC.1881
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal Organizational Files, 1960-2010
  - California Dance Educators Association (CDEA) Newsletters., 1973-2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Winter 1992; winter 1998; summer, fall 2001; spring, summer 2002; spring, summer 2003 "CDEA Newspost." Jan. / Feb., fall 1973; spring 1974; spring 1975 "CDEA Newsletter."
  - Calouste Gulbekian Foundation., undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Brochure for ACARTE in English and Portuguese.
  - Campbell, Joseph., 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Magazine and newsclippings. Initial invitation letter for membership to The Joseph Campbell Archives & Library Center for the Study of Depth Psychology.
  - Cantrell, Audre Norton., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Outline for Littlewheel Project. Ojo Caliente postcard and map.
  - Cardaro-Corradi, Janice Ann., 1993, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Resume. Correspondence about Elizabeth Rearick's movie "Dances of the Hungarians." Fulbright proposal draft to research Hungarian dance.
  - Carter, Jimmy., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Fulbright Prize Edition Newsletter. Carter awarded the Fulbright Prize for International Understanding.
  - Carter-Urick, Ellen Maureen., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    AFS recommendation for UCLA Film, Television, and Digital Media graduate school. Thank you letter.
  - Cassis, Kathryne., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Orpheus & Isadora Ltd. Letter.
  - Catterson, Pat., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Letter. Photocopy of newspaper articles.
  - Celebrations., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Note from Corporation for Public Broadcasting Carolynn Reid-Wallace about film "Celebration: A world of art and ritual." Solicitation letter for celebration of cultural traditions films.
  - Center for Movement Education and Research (CMER)., 2003 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Brochure.
  - Champion, Marge., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Obituary for the eight-decade dancer, choreographer.
  - Champlin, Chuck., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Outreach letters for "The Just Think Foundation" that develops programs to educate children about media.
  - Chapman, John., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    AFS letter of recommendation.
  - Chandler, Deborah., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Letter and abbreviated version of dissertation "Dancer and the Livebody: Revising the dance ideal."
  - Cheney, Gay., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Clark, Sharon Leigh., 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Letter of recommendation. Correspondence.
  - Clarke, Sir Arthur C.., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Newsclipping. Letter.
  - Clarke, Martha., 1987-2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Jan. 18, 1987 New York Times Magazine newsclipping. Fall 2004 "Lincoln Center Theater Review."
  - Clarke, Theodore C.., undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    "Voyager: An exploration of origins" at JPL.
  - Coburn, Melissa Anne., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Senior thesis project "Perspectives in the Anthropology of Dance."
  - Cochrane, Louise Morley., 2003-2008 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Cogburn, Elizabeth., 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    New Song Ceremonial House informational flyer.
  - Coggan, Forrest., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Letter with photocopy of photo.
  - Cohen, Selma Jeanne., 2006 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Dance historian's obituary. Correspondence.
  - Coleman, Elinor., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Informational packet with photos. Letter plus CV sheet.
  - Columbia University., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Correspondence concerning AFS application as professor of Dance.
  - Colvey, Cornell., 1992 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Letter to Beverly Robinson. Thesis draft "The Value of a Master: The development of Capoeira in the United States cities Boston (1986-1992) / Los Angeles (1979-1985)."
  - Conrad-Da'oud, Emilie., 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Continuum innovative movement seminars informational brochures.
  - Conseil International de la Danse (CID) International Dance Council (IDC)., 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Informational brochure of dance competitions with formal relationships with UNESCO. "Tradition and Art" in Greek.
  - Cootz, Yvonne Marie., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Memorial notices for the Dance Ethnology graduate.
  - Cordova, D. C.., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Excellerate Learning Institute correspondence and informational materials.
  - Coros, Mary., 1980-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    CV. "Knowledge and Meaning: How does it come to be? Where is it located? In it? In me? In you?" "S and S (Sousta and Sex)." "Enroute Towards Understanding Gadamer and Dance Without a Method." "Sousta." "Understanding How to Understand Subjective Dance Experience." Correspondence, photos, fellowship application.
  - Correa, Charles M.., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Greetings rendering on tissue paper.
  - Coryell, M. Dorothea Smith., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Bennington Alumni Magazine article.
  - Council of Dance Administrators (CODA)., 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    "The Education, Training, and Development of Dance Educators in Higher Education" by Elizabeth Hayes. Nov. 1977 conference Summary Notes on standards developed. June 1977 Agenda and Summary Notes. Correspondence. May 1980 Agenda. Nov. 1975 Summary Notes.
  - Council Grove III Community Elementary School., 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    1977 catalog of Compton, CA public school. "An Inner City School Response to the Question: In what form should public education survive?" by Lola Hanson. Board of Directors meeting minutes 1978-1980 including address list of Board of Directors, Budget, and By Laws. Two scripts in-progress of oral histories done by the students "Illuminations from Mrs. Enriquez's Childhood" and "Illumination from the Oral Histories of Mrs. Georgia and Oliver and Senora Velia Enriquez." "Heritage Theatre: Developing the Tools of Ethnography and Historiography with Elementary School Children" by Hanson, Rinzler, Schley.
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars-First Advisory., 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Annual Report 1980-1981. Fulbright-Hays Act screening committee information.
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars-Second Advisory (1 of 2)., 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Booklets about the American Fulbright scholars, "Board of Foreign Scholarships Report on Exhanges," "Fulbright Lecturing and Research Awards Abroad," "Board of Foreign Scholarships Fulbright Program Exhanges," "Fulbright Scholars-in- Residence."
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars-Second Advisory (2 of 2)., 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    AFS served as screening consultant in dance. Informational brochures about the application process for different geographic regions and years. Eleanor Campbell King and Winifred Rosa Widener 1980/81 applications that were reviewed. Notes and correspondence.
  - Craft & Folk Art Museum (CAFAM)., 1984-1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Nov. / Dec. 1988 calendar. 1984 and 1988 Festival of the Masks celebration booklets. Memorial notice for Edith R. Wyle, CAFAM founder.
  - Critchlow, Keith., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Photocopied drawings for movement notation. Included are "Vector Register for the Eight Effort Actions," "Conversion of Eight Effort Actions," and "Twelve Diametral Directions Meet the Eight Diagonal Effort Actions."
  - Cross-Cultural Dance Resources (CCDR)., 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Brochures. Correspondence. Event notices. Spring 2003 Newsletter honoring AFS as keynote speaker at Northern Arizona University. Spring 1991, summer and winter 2001, summer and autumn 2002, spring and Dec. 2003, spring/summer 2004 Newsletters.
  - Crowley, Daniel., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Dec. American Folklore Society News.
  - Cunningham, Merce., 2002-2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Newsclippings and fundraising requests.
  - Cushing, Frank H.., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Aug. Smithsonian article.
  - Dalai Lama., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    "Yoga Journal" article.
  - Dalldorf, Ose., 1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Correspondence. Informational postcard.
  - Dally, Lynn., 2006 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    "On Tap" article.
  - Dalton School., 1996-2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Correspondence. Informational packet, brochures, articles. Fall 2002 "Connections."
  - d'Amboise, Jacques., 1963-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    June 21 "Life Magazine" article. "He Makes Me Feel Like Dancin'" flyer.
  - Dance Art Museum., 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Correspondence. Informational press release.
  - Dance Critics Association (DCA)., 1948, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    "Black Mountain College and Merce Cunningham in the Fifties" symposium. Correspondence. Personal note from Merce Cunningham to AFS. DCA booklets. Photocopies of 1948 correspondence to Buckminster Fuller from Josef Albers, Bob Orr.
  - Dance Critics Association (DCA) News (1 of 2)., 2002-2006 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Spring, summer/autumn 2002; Spring, summer 2003; fall 2004; summer, winter 2005; fall/winter 2005-2006.
  - Dance Critics Association (DCA) News (2 of 2)., 1995-2001 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Summer 1995; spring, summer 1996; autumn 1997; spring, summer/autumn, winter 1998; winter 1999; winter 2000; autumn/winter 2000-2001; spring/summer 2001.
  - Dance Database Project (DDBP) (1 of 2)., 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    1988 proposal. Meeting minutes. Correspondence. "Dance on Disc: The complete catalog of the dance collection of the New York Public Library."
  - Dance Database Project (DDBP) (2 of 2)., 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    "Dance Database Project: Dance: International index and abstracts" NEH proposal by Elsie Dunin.
  - Dance Films Association., 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Annual meeting notification.
  - Dance Heritage Coalition., 1993-2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Scholars in Residence. Brochures. National Initiative to Preserve America's Dance (NIPAD) information guide. Press releases. "America's Irreplaceable Dance Treasures: The first 100" nomination form and information. Sum 1999 "After Images." "Sustaining America's Dance Legacy: How the field of Dance Heritage can build capacity and broaden access to dance in the next ten years, Oct. 2000." 2003 "Dance Videotapes at Risk" and "A Copyright Primer for the Dance Community."
  - Dance and Media., 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Online and newsclippings.
  - Dance Notation Bureau (DNB)., 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Fall 2002 and spring, fall, winter 2003 Bulletin.
  - Dance Resource Center (DRC)., 1981-2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    "Lester Horton Awards" programs, ballots, invitations. 1981 update of 1965 proposal "The Development of a Dance Film Archives at UCLA" by Alma Hawkins.
  - Dance Resource Center (DRC) Dancezine (1 of 2)., 2002-2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Jan./Feb., May/June, July/Aug., Nov./Dec. 2002; Jan./Feb. 2003; July/Aug. 2004; Jan./Feb., March/April, July/Aug., Sept./Oct. 2005; Nov./Dec. 2006.
  - Dance Resource Center (DRC) Dancezine (2 of 2)., 1993-2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    March/April 1993; July/Aug., Sept./Oct., 1998; July/Aug., Sept./Oct., Nov./Dec. 2000, Jan./Feb., March/April, May/June, July/Aug., Sept./Oct., Nov./Dec. 2001.
  - Dancescape., 1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    July edition. Brochures.
  - Dance South LA., 2009 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Informational packet. Nate Holden Performing Arts Center symposium schedule. Certificate of Appreciation to AFS.
  - Danforth, Loring M.., 1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Photocopy article "Tradition and Change in Greek Shadow Theater" July-Sept. Journal of American Folklore.
  - Daniel, Yvonne Payne (1 of 2)., 1983-1984, 1990s (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Correspondence. "Dancing Down River: A presentation on the dance of Suriname." "What is Ethnic Dance?" "In the Company of Women in Cuba." "Economic Vitamins from the Cuban Aesthetic System or Commoditization and Cultural Conservation in Cuban Tourism." "Religious Ritual in a Secular Society: African and European traditions in contemporary Cuba." "A Pluralist's View of Multicultural Education or Towards the Creation of New Structure Through Dance/Music." "Changing Values Manifested in Cuban Rumba." "Popular Culture in Cuba: Changing values." "The Potency of Dance: A Haitian examination."
  - Daniel, Yvonne Payne (2 of 2)., 1989-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Smith College course descriptions. Correspondence. CV.
  - Dannenberg, Penelope Levitt., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Correspondence with New York Foundation for the Arts Director of Artists' Fellowships.
  - Darwin., 2005 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    "Darwin: The devolution of a believer" by John Darnton.
  - Davidson, Gordon., 2005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    June "Privilege: Celebrating philanthropy" article.
  - Davis, Ron., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Correspondence concerning a loan from AFS.
  - deMille, Agnes., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Newsclippings.
  - deMille, Rosalind Jane., 2009 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Memorial flyers.
  - Denby, Edwin., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Book review and clipping.
  - Descutner, Janet Wynn., 1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Design Dimension Project., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Proposal.
  - DeVarco, Tony and Bonnie., 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Personal correspondence. Exhibition postcard.
  - Diaghilev, Serge., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Dibia, I Wayan., 2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Body Tjak / Los Angeles Fowler Museum flyer.
  - Dillihay, Ernest., 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Correspondence with Director of Cultural Affairs Department for the City of Los Angeles about Dance Dialogue.
  - Dinerman, Margaux Eve., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Correspondence concerning dropping courses. "Saint Lazaro: Myth, song, and dance."
  - Dixon-Stowell, Brenda., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    "Dancing in the Dark: The life and times of Margot Webb in Aframerican vaudeville of the swing era."
  - Dorris, George., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    AFS prepared for Buckminster Fuller's 100th "Experience and Experiencing." Correspondence.
  - Dosamantes-Alperson, Erma., 1979, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    "The Intrapsychic and the Interpersonal in Movement Psychotherapy" and "Working with Internalized Relationships Through a Kinesthetic and Kinetic Imagery Process."
  - Drewal, Margaret Thompson., 1988 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    "From Rocky's Rockettes to Liberace: The politics of representation in the heart of corporate capitalism."
  - Duke, Jerry., 1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Dance 226C grant proposal.
  - Duncan, Isadora., 1982, 1987, 2002-2009 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    AFS "Text for Isadora Duncan Slide Show/Video." Commercial recording- "Twilight of the Gods: The essential Wagner collection." A photo of unnamed ruins. National Museum of Women in the Arts brochure and press release. Feb. 1982 "Ballet News." Bibliography of Duncan material. Letter from K. K. Hanna.
    Includes 1 CD.
  - Duncan, Isadora video., 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Correspondence about copyrights. "Isadora in a New Perspective" 1967. "The Lucky 13th Annual Somatics Conference." 25th Anniversary Season at the Isadora Duncan International Institute "Sacred Topographies: The body and the land."
  - Dunham, Katherine., 1993-2007 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Obituary. Newsclippings. "Katherin Dunham: Dance on camera" flyer. 2002 flyer for International Dance Day, UNESCO. "Dance in America on Great Performances" informational packet. Fall 1993 "Dance Notations." Oct. 2002 "Library of Congress Information Bulletin."
  - Dunin, Elsie., 1979, 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Correspondence. 1979 "Social Responsibilities of a Dance Study Within One's Own Subculture-South Slavic / American."
  - DuPeron, Lori., 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    CV.
  - D'Urso, Karen., 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dymaxion Dance Group., 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Chloe Scott letter.
  - Eames, Ray and Charles., 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Eames Foundation brochure. "Work of Charles and Ray Eames: A legacy of invention" exhibit brochure. Gallery and store 2002 catalogue.
  - Ecker, Suzanne., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    CVs.
  - Eichenbaum, Rose., 1995, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    "Master of Movement: Portraits of America's dance makers" written by Eichenbaum about her photos, promotional postcards. Fall 1995 "Reform Judaism." AFS photo release form.
  - Eisler, Laurie., 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Letter and CV.
  - Eldredge, Letitia., 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Personal notes to AFS and promotional postcards.
  - Eliade, Mircea., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    New York Times obituary.
  - Enters, Angna., 1989 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Photocopy of obituary clipping.
  - Erdman, Jean (1 of 2)., 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    "The Coach with the Six Insides" program notes and Feb. 17-29, 1964 UCLA Concerts program. International promotional flyers, poster, photos. AFS letter to Joseph Campbell regarding filming "The Coach with the Six Insides."
  - Erdman, Jean (2 of 2)., 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Photo proofs of "The Coach with the Six Insides." Script and key points of action by act.
  - Erhard, Werner., 1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Dec. 29 Los Angeles Times newsclipping about the Est founder.
  - Erlanger, Margaret., 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Correspondence with Director of Graduate Program at University of Illinois and Urbana-Champaign concerning dance on film and AFS professional recommendations.
  - Ervin, Shelley., 1990-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Correspondence about "The Teen Well Being Program: A pilot project for at-risk teens teaming the wellness, environmental and arts communities."
  - Esponda, Susan., 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Family newsletter[?]
  - Estate Project for Artists with AIDS., undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    "A Life in Dance" booklet to assist artists plan for their artistic legacy.
  - E.T.a. F Szeto., 1993-1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Personal letters to Snyders, some unopened.
  - Everybody Dance, Now., 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Magazine clipping. Thirteen / WNET press release about "Teacher's Curriculum Guides Will Reach Every High School Across the Country." See also Box 83, folders 1-4.
  - EZTV., 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    "John Dorr & EZTV Timeline 1979-1993."
  - Fahmy, Melda (Farida)., undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Flyer of book about AFS former student "Daughter of Egypt: Farida Fahmy and the Reda Troupe" by Franken.
  - Feld, Steven., undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Photocopy of book chapter "Linguistic Models in Ethnomusicology."
  - Felton, Susan Kennedy., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    AFS graduate student who uses film to document movement. Letter to John Mueller.
  - Ferry, John., 2007 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    "Sitting Bull: A Stone in my Heart" film promotional postcard, articles.
  - Film-Contemporary Trends., 1993-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Program "Festival Renania Do Norte-Vestefalia." Newsclippings. Human Kinetics 2001 Dance resources catalog.
  - Fitzgerald, Bob and Lutie., 1936, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    50th anniversary photos, invitation. Photocopies of Frances Graves Sweeney's letter to her mother, Rebecca Graves. "My On-Going Quest for 'Education'" by Robert Fitzgerald.
  - Fitzpatrick, Michael., 2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    "Music of Compassion" flyers.
  - Fleishman, Sue., 1988-2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Stanley and Doris Fleishman memorial notes. Postcard.
  - Florida International University., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Informational packet and correspondence. "Dancing Across Disciplines" at the Intercultural Dance and Music Institute.
  - Forner, Michelle L.., 1993? (Box 12, Folder 15)
    CV and arts administrator essay.
  - Foster, Sir Norman., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Photocopy of "Letter From Europe: Living with Berlin, How do you rebuild a city that wants to settle its account with the past, but can't decide what its future should be?" article about the architect for Reichstag.
  - Foster, Susan., 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    WAC 220 seminar: World Dance Histories. Re-choreographing World Dance presentation "Choreographers and Choreographies." AFS Keynote address for the 13th Annual Dance Ethnology Forum. "Past, Present and Future."
  - Francis, Sam., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Museum of Contemporary Art exhibit brochure.
  - Frank, Letitia Evans., 2009 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Memorial note.
  - Fried, Otto., 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Personal letter.
  - Friedman, Willow Young., 1990-2005 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    AFS letter of recommendation. CV.
  - Frosch-Schroder, Joan D.., 1991-1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    AFS letter of recommendation. CV. Tenure and Promotion Packet to University of Maryland at College Park. Photocopy of "A Global View: Dance appreciation for the 21st century" article. "Things of Significance Do Not Vanish: Dance and the transmission of culture in the Ghanaian community of Greater Washington, D.C." "Moving Communities: Dance in contexts of culture and power."
  - Fuller, Loie., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    1862-1928 lighting for dance on stage. "Goddess of Light" book review.
  - Fuller, Margaret., 1978, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    "The Letters of Margaret Fuller" multiple volumes book reviews. "Margaret Fuller, Critic: Writings from the New York Tribune, 1844-1846" book review.
  - Galle, H. K.., 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Ethnology on film correspondence with editor of "Encyclopaedia Cinematographica."
  - Gantz, Judithe Siegel., 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    CV and personal statement. AFS letter of recommendation for promotion within UCLA Dance Department. Center for Movement Education and Research, Director.
  - Geertz, Clifford., 1989, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Obituary. "Works and Lives: The anthropologist as author" book review. Photocopy of chapter "Ethos, World-View and the Analysis of Sacred Symbols" used as reading in Ethnic Arts 190.
  - Gehry, Frank., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Pritzker Architecture Prize brochure.
  - Geiogamah, Hanay., 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    CV. AFS letter of recommendation.
  - Georges, Robert A., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Photocopies of "The Relevance of Models for Analyses of Traditional Play Activities" for Ethnic Arts 190 and "Toward an Understanding of Storytelling Events."
  - Gerber, Alex., 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Letters about his book "Wholeness: On education, Buckminster Fuller and Tao."
  - Getty Center., 1984, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Nov. 26, 1984 "Newsweek" article. Dec. 3, 1998 "The New York Times On the Web" article.
  - Ghei, Kiren., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    AFS letters of recommendation.
  - Gilbert, Pia., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    "Celebrating Pia Gilbert and Her Music in Honor of Her 80th Birthday" booklet.
  - Gilbert, Tamara B., 1977, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    AFS letters of recommendation. CV. Photocopy of "Dorothi Bock Pierre and the Dance Collection Try to Dispel the Notion That Most Dancers Know Nothing About Their Art…" article.
  - Gimblett, Maxwell., 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Personal letter. Exhibit promotional article and flyer. "Objects of Alchemy" exhibit brochure for Artis Gallery.
  - Ginzburg, Carlo., 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Dec. 15, 1991 New York Times "Was the World Made Out of Cheese?" article about Ginzburg. Draft of "Montaigne, Cannibals, and Grottoes."
  - Girard, Alexander., undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Brochure for the Cooper-Hewitt, National Design Museum exhibit "The Opulent Eye of Alexander Girard."
  - Giurchescu, Anca., 1986-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Correspondence about trip to Poland "ICTM Study Group on Ethnochoreology." 1986 Yearbook for Traditional Music article "Power and Charm. Interactrion of Adolescent Men and Women in Traditional Settings of Transylvania." Flyers for book "Romanian Traditional Dance: A contextual and structural approach."
  - Glascock, Baylis and Kathy., 1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Article about gardening.
  - Glushanok, Peter., 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Anthology of Film Archives "Peter Glushanok Film Tribute" press release.
  - Goldstone, James and Cookie., 1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)